Guide to the Tree Top, Inc. Records 1938-2009
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Tree Top, Inc. Records
1938-2009
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 https://libraries.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
Cage 785
Tree Top, Inc.
15 linear feet of shelf space 20 boxes plus oversize
The collection includes historic corporate records, photographs, and ephemera of Tree Top, Inc.
Tree Top, Inc. is a fruit processing cooperative headquartered in Selah, Washington. Bill Charbonneau founded the enterprise in 1944 as a private company, shortly after he and his family moved to Washington from Southern California. He purchased a small apple processing plant, first operating under its existing name, Pomona Products, then changing the name to Charbonneau Packing Corporation in 1946. He introduced the Tree Top apple juice brand in 1947. In 1960, a small local group of farmers joined together and created a grower cooperative, buying out Charbonneau's company and the Tree Top name. Since then, Tree Top, Inc. has operated continuously as a cooperative.
The collection includes historic corporate records, photographs, and ephemera of Tree Top, Inc. In addition to the cooperative's records, the collection also includes earlier materials from from Tree Top's predecessor company, which was owned by Bill Charbonneau. The collection also contains oral histories and other materials created during company-sponsored history projects in 1980, 2003, and 2008-2010.
The collection was organized by Amanda Van Laren when Tree Top, Inc. loaned the records to historian David Stratton to support his research for a book-length company history. This arrangement has been retained. The collection is organized in five series:
Series 1: Management Records, 1956-2009. This series consists of records related to the management and operation of Tree Top, Inc. including the grower newsletter Tree Topics (1968-1997), Apple Corps, plant newsletters, annual reports, growers' contracts, and information on cooperatives.
Series 2: Public Relations, 1963-2004. This series consists of records related to Tree Top public relations, including press releases and articles related to Tree Top or the juice industry.
Series 3: Advertising, 1950s-2008. This series consists of Tree Top advertisements and promotions, including copies of advertisements, product labels, and promotional brochures.
Series 4: History, 1938-2008. This series includes textual documents and media relating to Tree Top's history, as well as a large sequence of photographs (both documentary and advertising), and other visual materials. It is divided into four subseries:
Subseries 4.1: History files. This subseries consists of a variety of textual documents. Some were gathered together as key sources for David Stratton's research for his book, "Tree Top: Creating a Fruit Revolution," and others were created in the course of his project planning and execution. It includes a small amount of material related to founder Bill Charbonneau; earlier company histories in various formats ("The Tree Top Story," materials from 2003 employee oral histories, and historic fact sheets); related notes and compiled historical data; and oral history project documentation.
Subseries 4.2: Photographs. This subseries consists of photographs (color and black and white prints and negatives) of Tree Top facilities, employees, and events, as well as photographs produced for advertising.
Subseries 4.3: Audiovisual and electronic media. This subseries consists of audio recordings of oral histories, miscellaneous video recordings, and digital files of corporate minutes.
Subseries 4.4: Oversized materials. This series consists of large-format items, including advertisements, newspapers, mounted photographs, artwork, and posters.
Series 5: Artifacts. This series consists of promotional or souvenir items and other realia.
The oral history audio recordings from Series 4, Box 17 were digitized in March 2021. The audio files are retained both as unedited wav files and as speed-corrected mp3 files in MASC’s archival digital storage.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Tree Top, Inc. donated this collection to the Washington State University Libraries in 2012 (MS 2012-24).
Files related to David Stratton's book, "Tree Top: Creating a Fruit Revolution" were removed from the collection and processed separately as David Stratton Papers on Tree Top, Inc., 1960-2010 (Cage 786)
David Stratton Papers, circa 1890s-2013 (MSSM.022)
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Tree Top, Inc. -- Archives; Tree Top, Inc. -- History -- Sources
Apple industry -- Washington (State) -- History -- Sources
Agriculture; Washington (State)
- Series 1: Management Records, 1956-2005
  - Tree Topics (grower newsletter), 1968-2004 (Box 1, Folder 01.01-01.10)
  - Tree Topics (grower newsletter), photocopies, 1968-1997 (Box 1, Folder 01.11-01.19)
  - Apple Corps newsletter (monthly), 1992-2005 (Box 2, Folder 01.20-01.25)
  - Corporate personnel growth charts and copies of headquarters building plans, Circa 1981 (Box 2, Folder 01.26)
  - Feasibility study of Tree Top, Inc. acquisition of Chelan Packing Co., 1968 March 14 (Box 3, Folder 01.27)
  - Report: Klahre, J.E. "Trend of Apple Production in Central Washington, 1959-1975.", 1969 (Box 3, Folder 01.28)
  - Tonnage totals 1956-1972 by state, type, and district; contracts from growers, 1965; list of growers (Undated), 1956-1972 and Undated (Box 3, Folder 01.29)
  - Articles:, 1968-1976 (Box 3, Folder 01.30)
  - Herzberg, Frederick. "One More Time: How Do You Motivate Employees?" Harvard Business Review (January-February, 1968). Reprint, Undated (Box 3, Folder 01.30)
  - MacKenzie, R. Alec. "The Management Process in 3-D." Harvard Business Review (November-December 1969). Reprint, Undated (Box 3, Folder 01.30)
  - Walton, Richard E. "How to Counter Alienation in the Plant." Harvard Business Review (November-December, 1972). Reprint, Undated (Box 3, Folder 01.30)
  - Brochure. "Personal Achievement Formula: An Exercise in Assessment and Career Planning." Telometrics International, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 01.30)
  - Butler Learning Systems. "Action-Oriented Supervision," 1978. Scripts for Human Resources audio slide show. Numbers 1-7, 1978, Undated (Box 3, Folder 01.30)
  - Tree Top. "Action-Oriented Supervision," Numbers 1-7. Instructional workbooks for the Butler Learning Systems program, Undated (Box 3, Folder 01.30)
  - Results Management Handbook prepared for Northwest Food Processors Association by Norman D. Willis and Associates, Undated (Box 3, Folder 01.31)
  - Miscellaneous reports; blank transfer forms and apple inventory sheets, Undated (Box 3, Folder 01.32)
  - Miscellaneous management documents, 1961-1985; stock certificates, 1961 and 1968; Base Capital Plan, 1977; Grower contracts and articles of incorporation, 1983; Articles of Incorporation and By-Laws, 1985, 1961-1985 (Box 3, Folder 01.33)
  - Landis, Dick and Jan. "Tree Top: Regional Co-op Finds Risks and Rewards in National Marketplace." Western Fruit Grower (September, 1983). Reprint, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 01.34)
  - Torgerson, Randall E. "Issues in Cooperative Marketing and Finance in the Mid-1980s." Address to the 25th Annual Meeting of Tree Top Cooperative, Yakima, Washington. November 7, 1984, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 01.35)
  - Equity proposal and documents on Equity Program, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 01.36)
  - Miscellaneous management documents, 1986-1987; clippings from 1986 Tree Topics; Equity Program; letters to growers regarding payouts and tonnage; earnings statements., 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 01.37)
  - Miscellaneous management documents, 1988-1989; Equity Program; membership agreements; tonnage received, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 01.38)
  - A Feasibility Report for the Expansion of the Tree Top Grape Facility in Sunnyside, Washington. September 27, 1989, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 01.39)
  - Miscellaneous management documents and reports, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 01.4)
  - Tree Top Historic References Guide, 1993 November (Box 4, Folder 01.41)
  - Employee Survey, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 01.42)
  - Miscellaneous management documents and reports; Tree Top Field Program, 1994-2002 (Box 4, Folder 01.43)
  - Corporate Volunteer Council of Yakima, 1999; draft of by-laws; correspondence; flyers and brochures, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 01.44)
  - Tree Top annual reports, 1975, 1977-1981, 1983-2009 (Box 4-5, Folder 01.45-01.50)
  - Tree Top Apple Quarterly (Winter 1997, Fall 1997, Spring 1998); Tree Top Ingredients News (Summer 1998-Spring 2004), 1997-2004 (Box 5, Folder 01.51)
  - The Apple Press newsletter (January 1997); Prosser Plant newsletter (1997 and 2001); MFO News, Milton-Freewater Plant newsletter (October 2002, January 2003), 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 01.52)
  - Seeds of Information, Selah Plant newsletter, 1997 June -2000 December (Box 5, Folder 01.53)
  - Seeds of Information, Selah Plant newsletter, 2001 January-February; 2004 June-August (Box 5, Folder 01.54)
  - Peeler Press, Wenatchee Plant Newsletter (November-December 1996); Slices and Dices, Wenatchee Plant newsletter (1997 March-2000 April), 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 01.55)
  - Corporate guest books (2 items), 1989-2001 and Undated (Box 15)
- Series 2: Public Relations, 1963-2004
  - Press releases and articles, 1963-1996 (Box 6-7, Folder 02.01-02.15)
  - "Apple and Pear Variety Production and Planting Trends in Washington State," prepared by Lindsay R. Buckner, Tree Top Vice-President, Field Services, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 02.16)
  - Press releases and articles, 1997-2004 (Box 7-8, Folder 02.17-02.31)
  - Washington Apple Commission "Healthy Choices for Kids" program, Module 1: "Eat a Wide Variety of Foods.", 1992 (Box 8, Folder 02.32)
  - Washington Apple Commission "Healthy Choices for Kids" program, Module 2, "Choose a Healthy Lifestyle," 1993; Module 3, "Eat Plenty of Fruits and Vegetables," 1994; Module 4, "Choose Healthy Snacks," 1995, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 02.33)
  - Washington Apple Commission "Healthy Choices for Kids" program; newspaper articles and press releases; sample endorsement letters, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 02.34)
  - Washington Apple Commission "Healthy Choices for Kids" program: Teacher's Guide, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 02.35)
  - Washington Apple Commission "Healthy Choices for Kids" program: Workbooks, Lesson Plans, and Activity Guides, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 02.36)
- Series 3: Advertising, 1950s-2008
  - Rohm and Haas Reporter, volume 25 number 1 (1964 January-February; four copies). Contains article on Tree Top, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 03.01)
  - Photocopies of advertisements from the 1950s and 1960s; brochure (two copies): "An Apple a Day" from the Washington State Apple Commission; Charbonneau Packing Co. envelopes; television schedule for Tree Top sponsored programs in Los Angeles and Chicago; advertising brochure from New Orleans, October 1960, 1950s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 03.02)
  - Mounted color photos of grocery store displays, Undated (Box 9, Folder 03.03)
  - Charbonneau and Tree Top advertisements, 1950s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 03.04)
  - Tree Top advertisements, 1960s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 03.05-03.06)
  - Tree Top brochure, 1973 (5 complete copies and 1 partial copy), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 03.07)
  - Program for Seventh Annual Yakima Valley Shrine Club, 1974; marketing policies (Undated); Summary of Brand (Undated); text for advertising frozen juice (1969); company profile (1988); cider label; blank stationery (circa 1990-2008); recipe booklets; "How to Drink an Apple"; Tree Top brochure (1988), 1969-2008 (Box 9, Folder 03.08)
  - Tree Top CD-ROM Guide, 2002 (for a film produced by Imageworks Media Group, Pasco, Washington), 2002 (Box 9, Folder 03.09)
- Series 4: History, 1938-2008
  - Subseries 4.1: History files
    - Tree Top: The Story of Apple Juice (2 copies), Undated (Box 9, Folder 04.01-04.02)
    - 1960 address by Bill Charbonneau; 1963 Charbonneau letter regarding unions; Charbonneau obituary; Harvard Business School, "The Tree Top Case," 1969; article: "Apple Commission Origin Sketched" (Undated); photocopies of Charbonneau note cards, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 04.03)
    - Handwritten notes of interviews with Frank Curran and Jim Legat (Undated); article on Tree Top from book, Valley of the Strong: Stories of Yakima and Central Washington History (1974); 1981 high school History class presentation; 1981 list of employees; 1987 employee meeting notice; historic highlights from past issues of Apple Corps; article from November 1971 Frozen Food Age; "The Story of Tree Top, Inc." (1971); collection of letters and ephemera (letterhead, labels, etc.), 1970s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 04.04)
    - Tree Top marketing pamphlets (3 copies), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 04.05)
    - Transcription of discussion: Pat Moss, Hugh Burnett, and Wilbur Nelson, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 04.06)
    - Material for 2003 employee interviews; Pat Moss memo, May 15, 2003; list of interviewees and outline in preparation for compiling Tree Top history, 1937-1981; questions for history interviews; lists of interviewees; correspondence with interviewees; transcript of interview with Don Alyea; list of employee hire dates, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 04.07)
    - "The Tree Top Story" (historical sketch) with list of Tree Top Historic Highlights; Undated histories of Tree Top; Tree Top history from 1991 annual report; Corporate Office Building fact sheet; Tree Top History, 1988; list of management, 1988, 1988-1991 and Undated (Box 9, Folder 04.08)
    - Listing of Tree Top historic records loaned to David Stratton for company history project (list produced by Amanda Van Lanen), Circa 2009 (Box 9, Folder 04.09)
    - Tree Top History Project retiree interview transcripts: Alyea, Don; Colbert, Ray; Colleran, Dennis; Dennis, Bob; Hager, Ray; Jones, Russ; Morin, Joe; Slowe, Norm; Westberg, Maury; Workman, Inetta, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 04.29.01-04.29.10)
    - History of region and company (removed from binder), Undated (Box 14, Folder 04.30.01)
    - Interview notes and transcripts from company history interviews (index cards), 1980 (Box 16)
  - Subseries 4.2: Photographs
    - Plant equipment and operations (negatives and rolls of color positives), Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.09)
    - Advertisement images of juice bottles (negatives), Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.09)
    - Apple picking (negatives), Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.09)
    - Diskettes (3.5") with photographic images (digital files), 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 04.09)
    - Color and black and white photographs of corporate offices in Selah, WA, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 04.10)
    - NFPCA Award, 1997 September (Box 10, Folder 04.10)
    - AS400 System upgrade, 1998 January (Box 10, Folder 04.10)
    - Selah Plant
      - Selah Plant: Color and black and white photos of construction, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Greg Crow, Filler Technician, Selah Plant, 2002 November (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Group photos of Scott Dittmer, Toby Nowlin, Kevin Green, John Prather, Jerry Saxton, and Herb Liggett, 2004 April (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Group photos of Don Sharp, Joe Pacheco, David Trampush, and Dennis Hunt, 2004 April (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - KCPQ Seattle filming in Selah Plant, 1995 September (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Aerial photos of Selah complex, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Black and white photos of plant operations, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Jeannie Swedberg, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Diana McNamara, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Jason Whitman, Jerry Kobes, Kim Kirkevold, and Jeff Davis in Selah Warehouse, 1996 August (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Gayle Hellums, Selah Plant employee, posing with GED she earned through the Tree Top Learning Center, 1997 June (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Dennis Hunt, Selah Plant Instrument Tech, speaks to Perry Tech students on a tour of Selah Plant, 1999 October (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Chuck Johnson in dunk tank, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Peter Boucot, Manufacturing Supervisor, Selah Plant, 1998 July (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Nora Goodwater, Shipper technician, Selah Plant, 2002 November (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Bulk Receiving Construction, 2000 August (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Brent Gilley, Caser Operator, Selah Plant, 1998 June (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Carole Walters, Filler Operator, Selah Plant, 1998 June (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Bulk Receiving Plant tour, 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - New line running rectangular gallon apple juice, 2004 April (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Apple Sauce project team: Dan Symes, Tom Davis, Gary Morford, John Baranowski, Mike Hoffarth, and Diana McNamara, 1998 May-June (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Pat Smith, Filler Helper, 1998 June (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Selah Applesauce Line, 1998 June (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Chris Soto, Inspector-Sanitation, Selah Plant, 1998 June (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Kalvin Kastel, Labeler Operator, Selah Plant, 1998 June (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Richard Lilly, Selah Plant Lab, 1999 December (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Joe Pacheco, 2004 April (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Don Sharp, Joe Pacheco, David Trampush, Dennis Hunt, 2004 April (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
      - Semi truck outside of Selah plant, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.11)
    - Wenatchee Plant
      - Howard Bumgarner inspecting Red Delicious at Wenatchee Plant, 1999 October (Box 10, Folder 04.12)
      - Wenatchee Plant, 1972 June - 1976 May (Box 10, Folder 04.12)
      - Black and white photos of Wenatchee Plant Fire, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 04.12)
      - Dan Whaley, 1999 March (Box 10, Folder 04.12)
      - Greg Hoffman, 1999 March (Box 10, Folder 04.12)
      - Chuck Bauer, 1999 March (Box 10, Folder 04.12)
      - Kirk Brown and Cliff Davidson, Wenatchee Plant Mechanics, 1999 March (Box 10, Folder 04.12)
      - Wenatchee employees: Alan Jacobs, Lee Coodfield, Wanda Maxson, Kirk Brown, Tim Evans, and Bill Harvey, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.12)
    - Tree Top Learning Center
      - Exterior of Tree Top Learning Center building (5 photos), 1997 April (Box 10, Folder 04.13)
      - Gayle Hellums, Selah Plant, and Ino Hinson, Instructor (6 photos), 1997 July (Box 10, Folder 04.13)
      - Leadership Skills Development Team: Pete Romero, Ross; Nora Goodwater, Selah; Ardis Endres, Ross; James Wiley, Selah; Carl Rogers, Selah; Manual Rangel, Ross (2 photos), 1998 September (Box 10, Folder 04.13)
      - Ricky Newton, Yakima Valley Community College Instructor and Ranferi Arteaga, Ross Plant (3 photos), 1999 June (Box 10, Folder 04.13)
    - Community Events
      - Coat Drive: Tina Torres and Tracey McMurray, 1998 December (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Job Fair, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - March of Dimes Walk America, Yakima, WA, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Debbie Baughman and family, March of Dimes Walk America, Yakima, WA, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - March of Dimes Walk America, Yakima, WA, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - March of Dimes Walk America, Yakima, WA, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - United Way Day of Caring: Don Wilson, Kim Wangler, Ester Huey, Sandy Conrad, Helen Wilson, 1999 September (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Debbie Baughman with car magnets sold to support military families, 2004 September (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic, Wixon Park, Selah, WA, 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic: Lisa Baldoz, Tom Stokes, and Jason Whitman, 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic: Sue Graf, Rich Sowder, Greg Bainter, Jason Whitman, Don Wilson, 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic: Debi Flores, Chuck Johnson, 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic: Rich Sowder, Brad Nelson, and Jeannie Swedberg, 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic: Rich Sowder, Tom Stokes, Jeannie Swedberg, and Chris Kelley, 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic: Jerry Kobes and Georgia St. Aubyn, 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic: Peg Braden, Lynne Lamb, Pat Moss, Lynn Hoselton, and Georgia St. Aubyn, 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Corporate Employees Picnic: Nancy Buck, Steph Blair, Candi Gayken, and Diana Roeber (4 photos), 1998 August (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Debbie Baughman and daughter Melissa, winner of the John McAlister Memorial Scholarship, 1998 July (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Jordan Lehner, Perry Tech Tree Top Scholarship Winner, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Bake Sale to buy microwave: Debbie Baughman, Kim Wangler, Louie Hauser, 1982-83 (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
      - Debbie Baughman and Melinda Kile (Pulliam), 1982-83 (Box 10, Folder 04.14)
    - Advertising: Television and retail displays
      - 2x Health Club, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Black and white photo of stack of Tree Top cabs, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Black and white photos of box of Tree Top apples (5 items), Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Black and white photo of woman standing next to a Tree Top Juice dispenser, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Flight attendants serving Tree Top products in flight, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Man in apple costume setting up Tree Top booth, Undated (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Tree Top NRG smoothie booth (2 items), 2000s (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Flat Fruit Promotion (8 items), 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Selah Days Parade Fruit Rocketz Van (3 items), 2003 (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Tree Top juice on grocery store shelves, Circa 1990s-2000s (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - 2 photos of Kellogg's "Fruit Harvest" cereal featuring Tree Top dried apple pieces, 2003 June (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - 3 photos Apple Cinnamon Cheerios display at Fred Meyers, Yakima, WA, 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Boy drinking from Tree Top juice box, Circa 1990s-2000s (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Kiosk shops in Vladivostok, Russia, selling Tree Top products, 1994 October (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Tree Top Orchard Blends bottles, 1998 May (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Black and white photos of boys drinking Tree Top canned juice, Circa 1990s-2000s (Box 10, Folder 04.15.01)
      - Color photo of store display, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Point Barrow, AK, cook posing with Rainier apples and Tree Top juice, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Advertisement: "It's New: Refrigerator Bottle.", Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Black and white photo of woman serving cider at a grocery store promotion, Circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Black and white and color photos of Halloween merchandising display, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Tree Top product line (color transparencies), Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Black and white proof sheet of woman wearing "Tree Top Juice Cider Sipping Society" t-shirt, Undated (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Black and white proof sheets, C.F. Weber Photography, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Black and white photo, Awarding certificate for "Honorary Citizen of New Orleans," C.F. Weber, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)
      - Black and white print from C.F. Weber proof sheets of "Golden Apple Award for Western Broker.", 1976 (Box 11, Folder 04.15.02)